<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".AboutFragment">

    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/imageView2"
        android:layout_width="195dp"
        android:layout_height="191dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="108dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="108dp"
        android:src="@drawable/logo"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent" />

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/textView7"
        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:text="Welcome to Jtech!\n\nWe are overjoyed to have you among us. Enter a world of cutting-edge technology, where your computing requirements will be met perfectly. Jtech has something exceptional in store for you, whether you're a tech enthusiast, a seasoned professional, or a casual user.\n\nJtech takes great pleasure in providing high-quality products and services that enhance your digital experience to new heights. Our carefully chosen assortment of the latest gadgets, powerful computing equipment, and creative accessories ensures that you'll find exactly what you're looking for, suited to your interests and needs.\n\nRest assured that your satisfaction is our first priority as you explore our virtual refuge for tech enthusiasts. Our committed team of professionals is always available to help you with specialized advice at every step of your journey.\n\nJoin our ever-growing community of satisfied customers who have discovered the joy of seamless technology integration. We believe that technology should be an enabler, simplifying your life and amplifying your potential.\n\nThank you for choosing Jtech as your go-to destination for all things tech. Get ready to embark on an exciting adventure with us, where innovation knows no bounds.\n\nHappy browsing and happy computing!\n\nThe Jtech Team"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        android:paddingRight="5dp"
        android:paddingLeft="5dp"
        android:paddingBottom="10dp"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toBottomOf="@+id/imageView2" />


</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>